{
    "id": "b191591c20cd4b3c90cb965ff25bbcad",
    "title": "Would rather and had better",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "656577bca0d64b82a1e3e58bc60c73b9",
            "title": "Would Rather And Had Better",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I’d rather you ………………….. keep in touch with him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "don't",
                        "didn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ……………….. go through this.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hadn't to",
                        "didn't have to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You’d better ………………… a doctor.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "consult",
                        "consulted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "After the way he treated me, I wish I ..................... him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't marry",
                        "hadn't married"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I’d rather …………….. on Sundays.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "not to work",
                        "not work"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You had better ………………… your valuables in a locker.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "keep",
                        "to keep"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We had better …………………. for a drink.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "not stop",
                        "not to stop"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We could sack him right now, but ……………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "I wouldn't rather",
                        "I'd rather not"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ………………… there when they arrested him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "had been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish you ………………… take this personally.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "won't",
                        "wouldn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}